Guide to the Postcards of female and male impersonators and cross-dressing, circa 1900-1930.
Postcards of female and male impersonators and cross-dressing,
- France, 1900-1925 (Box 1)
  - Gallant scenes (Box 1)
    - Aristocrat and Flower Girl, 1911; 103; Edit. d’Art; 14.2 x 9.2 cm; Applied color. Divided verso. (Box 1, Folder 12)
      Eighteenth-century seduction scene: woman dressed as a male aristocrat woos a peasant-girl flower-seller against a studio backdrop of a sylvan scene.
    - Violinist, 1900; 104; 14.1 x 9.1 cm; Applied color (Box 1, Folder 12)
      Inscription: "Addressed to Mlle Fanny Grollier. Brief note at lower margin of recto signed Melanie B."
    - 1er Avril, 1905; 105; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. (Box 1, Folder 12)
      Series of 2 April Fool’s Day (“poisson d’avril”) postcards. A doggerel verse printed on the recto of each refers to the pair in the photo as “ces marquis gracieux.”
    - 1er Avril, 1905; 106; 14 x 9.2 cm; Applied color. Undivided verso. (Box 1, Folder 12)
      Series of two April Fool's Day postcards. A doggerel verse printed on the recto of each refers to the pair in the photo as "ces marquis gracieux".
    - Chasse-croise, 1900; 107-111; 9.1 x 14.2 cm; 5 postcards; Applied color (Box 1, Folder 12)
      Series of 5 postcards number I through V showing an 18th century picnic. The series is highly unusual as the only postcards of the genre documented to date that represent a cross-dressed woman and a man dressed as a man both portraying male roles. Inscription: "Addressed to Mesdemoiselles Bonnet; signed on recto of each card: Henriette."
    - Aristocrat and a country girl, Postmarked; 112-117; Stebbing; Kunzli Freres Editeurs; 14.2 x 9 cm; Applied color. Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 1, Folder 13)
      Captioned: Le Droit de passage, L'Invitation, Le Beau raisin, Le Goiter, and La Declaration. Same series depicted in cards 329-330.
    - L'invitation, 1903; 113, 115-117; Stebbing; Kunzli Freres Editeurs; 14.2 x 9 cm; Applied color. Divided verso. (Box 1, Folder 13)
      Set of four cards with photo narrative of an 18th-century seduction scene. Male impersonator as aristocrat woos a female country girl encountered on a footbridge. The captions recount the tale: “Le Droit de passage,” “L’Invitation,” “Le Beau raisin,” “Le Goûter,” “La Déclaration.” Notice printed full width indicating “Carte Postale. Tous le pays étrangers n’acceptent pas la correspondence au recto (se renseigner à la poste). Inscription: "Series of love notes addressed to a woman named Albertine Frémoul from a man identifying himself as “votre fiancé” (signature partially illegible: “G. Rammeno...”
    - L'invitation, 1900; 114; Stebbing; Kunzli Freres Editeurs; 14.2 x 9 cm; Applied color. Undivided verso. Inscribed. (Box 1, Folder 13)
      Variant edition of L'Invitation.
    - Idylle a trianon, 1902; 118-120; Manuel, Henri (1874-1947); 13.8 x 9.2 cm; 3 postcards; Applied color. Undivided verso. (Box 1, Folder 13)
      Set of three cards with photo narrative of an 18th-century seduction scene. Male impersonator as officer invites a female aristocrat to dance in a studio-set salon. Numbered I, II and X.
    - Il m'aime, Un peu, Beaucoup, 1905; 121-123; Stebbing; Kunzli Freres Editeurs; 13.9 x 9 cm; Applied color (Box 1, Folder 13)
      Series of three postcards of a woman dressed in late 18th-century officer's wear reacting to declarations from a woman in a dress and flowered hat. The woman is reciting the traditional French equivalent of “he loves me, he loves me not” while plucking petals from a flower. Cards numbered I, II and III. Each postcard after the first has a rhyming couplet as a caption on the recto.
    - Le Marquis Amoureux, 1904; 124-128; 14 x 9.3 cm; Applied color (Box 1, Folder 14)
      Complete series of five postcards showing a woman dressed as an 18th-century marquis courting another woman dressed as a female aristocrat, ending with a scene of the marquis stealing a kiss.
    - Shepard and shepardess, 1906; 129-134; 14 x 9.2 cm; 6 postcards; Applied color. Divided verso. (Box 1, Folder 14)
      Complete series of six postcards showing a young woman dressed as an 18th-century shepherd having a lover's spat with a young woman dressed as a shepherdess. Each postcard has one line of a six-line verse offering the dialogue of the lovers.
    - Aristocrat courting, 1902; 135-139; Walery; 14.1 x 9 cm; 5 postcards; Applied color (Box 1, Folder 15)
      Complete series of five postcards showing a woman dressed as an 18th-century male aristocrat who pays court to a woman in a flowered dress and with flowers in her hair. All the scenes are set against a blank studio backdrop.
    - Egg, 1903; 140-145; 13.9 x 9.2 cm; 6 postcards (Box 1, Folder 15)
      Complete series of six postcards showing an enormous egg in front of a painted backdrop of a bucolic landscape. Over the series, the egg opens into left and right halves to reveal a woman dressed as an 18th-century male aristocrat who pays court to a woman dressed as a female aristocrat. Postmarks show the cards were mailed successively during the course of two months, with a message on the final one in the photo-narrative stating, “Thanks, this is the last one.” The dates and inscription suggest how such series were sometimes used to sustain interest in a friendly correspondence over time. Postage stamp and postmark on one corner on verso of each card. Curved impression to corners of cards indicating the set was once place in a die-cut postcard holder. Inscription: "Addressed to Mademoiselle A. Lefort; signed on recto of each card: five signed G.M.; one signed Germaine. Brief message on lower right corner of recto of each card, two in English, the rest in French. Message on lastmailed card indicates “Merci, c’est la dernière.”
    - Amourette Louis XV, 1905; 146-150; 14 x 9 cm; Applied color (Box 1, Folder 15)
      Set of five postcards with a photo narrative of an 18th-century seduction scene involving a marquis and marquise. Each card includes a brief caption on near lower margin of the recto with a line of dialog. The first scene shows the female aristocrat seated by herself reading a book; the male aristocrat arrives and ultimately persuades her in the final scene. Same series depicted in cards 67-68 and 310.
    - Amoureux Viennois, 1905; 151; 14.2 x 8.8 cm (Box 1, Folder 15)
      One postcard (no. 3) from a series of unknown length representing a woman dressed as a male officer in a braided uniform. The officer kisses the hand of a seated woman wearing a braided dress designed to echo the uniform.
    - Pierrette et Polichinelle, 1900; 152; Manuel, Henri (1874-1947); A. Bergeret et Cie.; 9 x 14.2 cm; Undivided verso. Inscribed. (Box 1, Folder 15)
      Same series depicted in cards 333-335.
    - Amourette Louis XV, 1905; 310; 14 x 9 cm; Applied color. Undivided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 19)
      Same image in card 149. Same series depicted in cards 67-68, and 146-150.
    - L'Abbe, les fiances, 1905; 311-312; 14 x 9 cm; 2 postcards; Applied color. Divided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 19)
      Same series depicted in cards 82-83 and 313.
    - L'Abbe, les fiances, 1904; 313; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 19)
      Same series depicted in cards 82-83 and 311-312.
    - Notre amour cherchait le mystere, 1907; 314; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 19)
      Same characters and setting as portrayed in card 315.
    - Ce petit coin tranquille, 1905; 315; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 19)
      Same characters and setting as portrayed in card 314.
    - Colin et Jeannette, 1905; 316-317; 14 x 9 cm; Applied color. Divided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Le Galant Gondolier, 1904; 318; 14 x 9 cm; Applied color. Undivided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Hotel du Chariot d'Or, 1904; 319; 14 x 9 cm; Applied color. Undivided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Idylle a Trianon, 1902; 320-328; Manuel, Henri (1874-1947); 14 x 9 cm; Applied color. Undivided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 20)
      Same series depicted in cards 64-66.
    - Aristocrat and a country girl, 1905; 329-330; Stebbing; Kunzli Freres Editeurs; 14 x 9 cm; Applied color. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 21)
      Captioned: L'Invitation and La Declaration. Same series depicted in cards 112-117.
    - Le Petit Colporteur, 1905; 331-332; Stebbing; Kunzli Freres Editeurs; 14 x 9 cm; Applied color. Undivided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Pierrette et Polichinelle, 1900; 333-335; Manuel, Henri (1874-1947); 9 x 14 cm; Undivided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 21)
      Same series depicted in card 152.
    - Pierrot et Columbine, 1900; 336-339; 9 x 14 cm; Undivided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Le Petit Polichinelle, 1908; 340-344; Walery; 14 x 9 cm; Applied color. Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - La ronde du garde champetre, 1904; 345; 14 x 9 cm; Undivided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Humor (Box 1)
    - Illusion's perdues, 1920; 79; 13.8 x 8.7 cm; After engraving. Divided verso. (Box 1, Folder 9)
      Reproduction of a line-drawing caricature: Female impersonator undressing revealed to be a skinny man.
      Female impersonator
    - La plus serieuse des Lorientaises, 1917; 80; Arnaud et Nozais; 14 x 9; Inscribed. (Box 1, Folder 9)
      Mustachioed man dressed as a peasant woman carrying a basket and an umbrella.
      Nantes, France
    - Bergere et Berger, Postmarked; 153-154; 14.2 x 9 cm (Box 1, Folder 16)
      Series of two comic postcards of a shepherdess and a shepherd.
    - Bonne Annee, 1930; 155; 13.7 x 8.8 cm; Applied color. Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 1, Folder 16)
      Studio photo of a garconne, the French new young women of the 1920s who appropriated a variety of masculine privileges. Includes personal message about health issues, life troubles, hopes to see friend in the coming year."
    - Bonne Annee, 1907; 156; 14.2 x 9.3 cm; Applied color. Divided verso. (Box 1, Folder 16)
      Woman dressed as a mailman in front of a studio backdrop of a village gate. Divided verso. Publisher given as E.N., card number as 8179. Personal message addressed to “Chère amie” (Félice Pinty) signed Marguerite." Inscription: "New year’s greetings to “Ma chère Henriette” at Castle Hall School in Northampton, England; signed “Ton amie qui t’embrasse, Jeanne Lambert”
    - Bonne Annee, 1913; 157; 14.2 x 9.3 cm; Applied color. Divided verso. (Box 1, Folder 16)
      Woman dressed as a mailman in front of a studio backdrop of a village gate. Same model, costume and set as preceding card, but differing pose. Holding mail.
    - Bonne Annee, 1909; 158; 14.2 x 9.3 cm; Applied color. Divided verso. (Box 1, Folder 16)
      Woman dressed as a mailman in front of a studio backdrop of a village gate. Same model, costume and set as preceding card, but differing pose. Holding flowers.
    - Bonne Annee, 1909; 159; 14.2 x 9.3 cm; Applied color. Divided verso. (Box 1, Folder 16)
      Woman dressed as a mailman seen through a painted frame illustrating letters and a mail-carrying case.
    - Cleodinerie, 1903; 160; A. Bergeret et Cie; 14.1 x 9 cm (Box 1, Folder 16)
      Female impersonator wearing a wig, pearls and a flowered tutu posing as a ballerina with arms in fifth position. The card is a spoof of the celebrated dancer and demimondaine Cléo de Mérode (1875–1966). A doggerel verse printed in red on the recto refers to the dancer's charms as designed to "captiver un prince."
    - Mademoiselle, ecoutez-moi donc!, 1910; 161-166; 13.8 x 8.6 cm; 6 postcards; Divided verso. (Box 1, Folder 16)
      Complete series of six postcards showing a amle impersonator approaching a young woman and convincing her to learn how to ride the young man's bicycle. The narrative takes place in front of a painted studio backdrop of a Paris city scene. Each card includes a snippet of dialog between the two characters; the woman identifies herself in one as an “ouvrière dans une grande maison de Modes de la Rue de la Paix.” Imprinted “a utiliser seulement dans le régime intérieur (FRANCE, ALGERIE et TUNISIE).”
    - La bretagne pittoresque - la plus belle fille de Pont-Aven, 1915; 167; A. Waron; 13.9 x 9 cm (Box 1, Folder 17)
      Female impersonator with gray hair and handlebar moustache dressed in the traditional garb of a woman from Brittany, including a bigouden (starched lace headdress), and with a market basket on one arm and an umbrella under the other. Addressed to Monsieur Dumont; signed Horace (?). Message refers teasingly to representation of gender on postcard.
      Saint-Brieuc, France
    - Costumes poitevins, 1909; 168; 14 x 8.8 cm (Box 1, Folder 17)
      Addressed to Mademoiselle Gratecap. Depicts couple dressed in traditional garb of the Poitou region on the west coast of France.
      Niort, France
    - Les deux gosses, 1910; 169-171; 14.1 x 9 cm; 3 postcards; Applied color (Box 1, Folder 17)
      Three postcards (nos. 2, 3 and 4) from a series of unknown length recounting episodes adapted from the melodramatic novel Les Deux gosses (Jules Rouff et Cie., 1880) by the popular author and playwright Pierre Decourcelle (1856-1926). The "two kids" of the title are Fanfan, the son of a diplomat carted off and raised by a married pair of petty criminals, and Claudinet, the ragged natural son of the couple. Decourcelle subsequently adapted the novel as a drama; in an 1896 production at the Theatre de l'Ambigu in Paris, the characters of the two boys were cast as trouser roles for young actresses, with Fanfan played by Mlle. Melo and Claudinet by Mlle. Reye. In the postcard series, the models for the two boys likewise are male impersonators.
    - Melle (Deux-sevres) - Paysanne poitevine, 1900; 172; Jules Robuchon; 14 x 9.2 cm (Box 1, Folder 17)
      Comic postcard of female impersonator in the traditional garb of a Poitevin peasant woman. Addressed to Mademoiselle Legras Nadel.
      Poitiers, France
    - La merine a nastasie, 1909; 173; 14.1 x 9.1 cm (Box 1, Folder 17)
      Series of two postcards (with card 174) representing scenes and characters from La Merine à Nastasie (1902), a play by Yann Saint- Acer, written in the Saintongeais dialect of the west coast of France.
    - La merine a nastasie, 1906; 174; 9.1 x 14.1 cm (Box 1, Folder 17)
      Series of two postcards (with card 173) representing scenes and characters from La Merine à Nastasie (1902), a play by Yann Saint-Acer, written in the Saintongeais dialect of the west coast of France.
    - Mme Pipelet lit son feuilleton, 1904; 175-177; 9 x 14 cm; Applied color. Inscribed. (Box 1, Folder 17)
      Series of three postcards representing humorous scenes from the daily life of an older woman played by a female impersonator. Addressed to Louise Hautain.
    - Racettes de friandises - Gateau Suisse, 1900; 178; A. Bergeret et Cie.; 14 x 9.1 cm; Undivided verso. (Box 1, Folder 18)
      Addressed to Auguste Morel. Woman dressed as a chef wearing a toque, men's coat and men's 18th-century kneepants and hose while holding up a fluted cake pan. She leans against a decor suggesting a country kitchen. Printed in red at the bottom of the recto is a recipe for Swiss cake.
    - Le berceuse du gosselin, 1905; 179; 14.1 x 9.1 cm; Divided verso. (Box 1, Folder 18)
      Female impersonator holding a porcelain doll and dressed as a nanny in a lace cap and apron.
    - Type Marseillais, 1904; 180-184; Lacour, F.; 14 x 9 cm (Box 1, Folder 18)
      Series of five comic postcards depicting a male impersonator as a woman of Marseilles. Each card has a humorous caption giving a line of dialog. Three cards (numbered 370, 373 and 374), show a fishwife carrying a scale for weighing her goods.
    - Male impersonator as a soldier, 1915; 185; 13.9 x 9 cm; Divided verso. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Fils a papa, 1907; 186; 9 x 14; Divided verso. (Box 1, Folder 18)
      Novelty card montage of three photos of the same woman dressed in top hat, tails and knee britches gesturing to a rabbit sitting next to her on a bench. May represent a musical hall trained animal act. Message on verso addressed to "Mon cher Pierre" and signed "Jeanne."
    - Amour en Bretagne-les premiers baisers, 1910; 348; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 25)
      Pontivy, France
    - La chanson de Nanette, 1910; 349; Lejeune, A.; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 25)
      Argentan, France
    - La chanson de Nanette, 1910; 350; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Argentan - Nanette, v'la l'marchand d'noisettes, 1910; 351; Chalumeau-Michelli; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - En Vacances, 1900; 352; 14 x 9 cm; Undivided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - La femme avocat, 1900; 353; Morinet, A.; 9 x 14 cm; Undivided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Fevrier, 1905; 354; 14 x 9 cm; Applied color and glitter. Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Present! Si on a besoin de nous, nous sommes la, 1915; 355; Noyer, A.; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 25)
      Photochroms
    - Le trousseau e Rosalie, 1910; 356; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 25)
      Cherbourg, France
    - Young male impersonator in top hat and suit, 1910; 357; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Costume series (Box 1)
    - Couple in fancy dress, 1905; 187; 14.1 x 9.2 cm; Divided verso. (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Three muskateers and gardener, 1905; 188; 9.1 x 14.2 cm; Divided verso. (Box 1, Folder 19)
      Postcard of four women: three dressed as 17th-century musketeers and one dressed as a male gardener wearing a work apron and heavy clogs and holding a rake. The two women at the center are the same one who appear in the “Couple in Fancy Dress” postcard, and they are standing in the same garden.
    - Male impersonators in costume, 1905; 189; 9 x 14 cm (Box 1, Folder 19)
      Postcard showing six women posing in front of the entry to a brick building. Three are dressed in the simple outfits of working women, including one wearing a long white apron; the other three are male impersonators dressed as a gendarme in uniform; a judge in robe, collar and chapeau; and one in a frock coat and fedora.
    - Female impersonators posing with a touring car, 1905; 190; 9 x 14 cm; Divided verso. (Box 1, Folder 19)
      Postcard showing nine men posing in front of an open touring car on an estate with trees and buildings in the background. The man at the center is dressed as a grand society woman in a travel outfit including a heavy coat, flowered hat, fur muff and pocketbook. The men surrounding her are dressed in various costumes, including one likely as a chauffer, one as a butler with feather duster, one with a crêpe-de-chine false beard, and others in worker’s coats and caps.
    - Female impersonators in 17th century costumes, 1905; 191; 9 x 14 cm; Divided verso. (Box 1, Folder 19)
      Postcard showing eight men in 17th-century costumes, including two female impersonators. All are posed in front of a brick wall in a garden.
    - Female impersonators in costume, 1905; 192; Lasseron, E.; 8.8 x 13.8 cm; Divided verso. (Box 1, Folder 19)
      Postcard showing ten men in a variety of costumes, including four dressed as women in dresses and wigs. All are posed in front of an exterior wall.
    - Flamenco dancers and aristocrats, 1905; 193; 9 x 14 cm (Box 1, Folder 19)
      Postcard showing five men in costume, including two as a male-female couple of flamenco dancers and two as a male-female couple of 18th-century French aristocrats.
    - Historical Illustrations: Joan of Arc (Box 1, Folder 20)
      Joan, of Arc, Saint, 1412-1431--Portraits
    - Arrive a Chinon, 1905; 194; Walery; 14 x 9 cm; Applied color (Box 1, Folder 20)
      Historical scene showing Joan of Arc telling the dauphin of France that he will be crowned king at Reims. As is conventional for iconography of Joan during her period of combat, she wears men’s clothing—in this case, an elaborate doublet and riding boots. Conversely, this image steps outside the convention by including a halberd-bearer accompanying Joan; the footsoldier is played by a male impersonator. Inscription: "Addressed to Lucien Renault; signed “Ta soeurette [illegible]”.
    - Jeanne d'Arc, 1903; 195; A. Bergeret et Cie.; 14.1 x 9.1 cm; Undivided verso. Postage stamp and postmark on verso. (Box 1, Folder 20)
      Joan of Arc in a doublet, breastplate and helmet, holding a sword and battle standard against a smoky background. A doggerel verse printed in red at upper left on the recto recounts her victory over the English. Inscription: "Addressed to Jeanne Carlin. Brief unsigned message on recto."
    - Jeanne d'Arc, 1903; 196-204; 14.1 x 9.1 cm; Applied color (Box 1, Folder 20)
      Complete series of eight postcards portraying key moments in the history of Joan of Arc. Each card has a caption indicating Joan’s presence at a particular place, along with a date. The first postcard shows her dressed as a simple shepherd girl hearing mystical voices; the next five show her as the savior of France dressed in full armor, with a sword and battle standard, but with the long hair of a woman; the seventh shows her “devant ses juges” wearing a simple man’s doublet; and the final card shows her forcibly returned to women’s clothing, wearing a white gown while tied to the stake and licked by flames.
    - Jeanne d'Arc, victorieuse des Anglais dilvre Orleans, 1905; 347; 14 x 9 cm; Applied color. Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Sweden, 1910; 3 postcards (Box 1, Folder 21)
  Sweden
  - Music Hall, Theater, and Film (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Damimitator John Graffton, 1910; 205; Hertzberg, Oscar; Svenska Litografisk; 13.8 x 8.9 cm; Divided verso. (Box 1, Folder 21)
      Graffton, John
      Stockholm, Sweden
    - John Graffton - Damimitator, 1912; 206; Hertzberg, Oscar; 13.8 x 8.6 cm; Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - John Graffton, Krinolinparodist, 1910; 207; Svenska Litografisk; 13.9 x 8.9 cm; Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Damimitator John Graffton, 1905; 233; Svenska Litografiska; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - John Grafton, Damimitator, 1905; 234; Hertzberg, O.; 14 x 9 cm; Divided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Austria (Box 2)
  - Music Hall, Theater, and Film, 5 postcards (Box 2)
    - Betti Kuhn, weiblicher Gesangskomiker, preisgekront, 1910; 208; Steinbock, J.; 14 x 9.1 cm; Divided verso. Inscribed. (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Kuhn dressed as a gentleman with a top hat.
      Kuhn, Betti
      Vienna, Austria
    - Betti Kuhn, weiblicher Gesangskomiker, preisgekront, 1910; 209; Steinbock, J.; 14 x 9.1 cm; Divided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Kuhn dressed as a dandy with a monocle.
    - Betti Kuhn, weiblicher Gesangskomiker, preisgekront, 1910; 210; Steinbock, J.; 14 x 9.1 cm; Divided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Kuhn dressed as a man holding a fly fishing rod.
    - Betti Kuhn, weiblicher Gesangskomiker, preisgekront, 1910; 211; Steinbock, J.; 14 x 9.1 cm; Divided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Kuhn dressed in a military uniform holding a saber and a battalion flag.
    - Betti Kuhn, weiblicher Gesangskomiker, preisgekront, 1910; 212; Steinbock, J.; 14 x 9.1 cm; Divided verso. No inscription. (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Kuhn dressed in an informal suit, holding a cigarette.
- Belgium (Box 2)
  - Music Hall, Theater, and Film, 1 postcard (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Male impersonator as 18th-century aristocrat, 1915; 213; 14 x 8.8 cm; Inscribed. Divided verso. (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Spain (Box 2)
  - Music Hall, Theater, and Film (Box 2, Folder 6)